If you want peace, prepare for war.
John Wick: Chapter 3 - Parabellum is a action, thriller,
crime film directed by Chad Stahelski.
Super-assassin John Wick returns with a $14 million price tag on his
head and an army of bounty-hunting killers on his trail.
After killing a member of the shadowy international assassin’s guild, the High Table, John Wick is
excommunicado, but the world’s most ruthless hit men and women await his every turn.
John Wick, played by Keanu Reeves.
Sofia, played by Halle Berry.
Winston, played by Ian McShane.
Bowery King, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Zero, played by Mark Dacascos.
The Adjudicator, played by Asia Kate Dillon.
John Wick: Chapter 3 – Parabellum is a 2019 American neo-noir action thriller film directed by Chad Stahelski from a
screenplay by Derek Kolstad, Shay Hatten, Chris Collins, and Marc Abrams, based on a story by Kolstad.
The film is the direct sequel to John Wick: Chapter 2 (2017) and
the third installment in the John Wick film series.
It stars Keanu Reeves as the title character, alongside an ensemble supporting cast including Halle Berry,
Laurence Fishburne, Mark Dacascos, Asia Kate Dillon, Lance Reddick, Anjelica Huston, and Ian McShane.
The film takes place immediately after Chapter 2 and centers on John Wick going on the
run from a legion of hitmen after a bounty is placed for his murder.
In October 2016, Stahelski stated a third John Wick film was in the works; this was formally announced in June 2017,
after the returns of Reeves and Kolstad were confirmed, followed by Stahelski's return in January 2018.
Much of the returning cast and crew was confirmed that
following month, with new members joining that May.
Principal photography began that month and lasted through that November,
with filming locations including New York City and Casablanca.
John Wick: Chapter 3 – Parabellum had its premiere at the Regal Union Square in New York City
on May 9, 2019, and was released in the United States on May 17, by Lionsgate.
It received highly positive reviews from critics, with praise for the
action sequences, visual style, and Reeves's performance.
The film grossed $327.7 million worldwide and took just 10 days to
become the highest-grossing film in the franchise.
A sequel, John Wick: Chapter 4, was released in March 2023, and a
spin-off film, Ballerina, was released in June 2025.
The film explores themes of new york city, martial arts, bratva
(russian mafia), casablanca, morocco, secret society.
The tone is intense.